001games.com 2015-12-20

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy covers 001Games.com, This Privacy Policy explains how 001Games.com collects and utilizes both personal and non-personal information when you use our websites.

**WHY DO WE COLLECT PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

001Games.com collects personal information to improve the manner by which we operate and offer our products and services, communicate with you, and provide effective customer support. We will not share your personally identifiable information with third parties without your consent, unless necessary for the purposes set forth in this Privacy Policy.

**WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**

Personal information specifically identifies an individual and may include: name; email address; and phone number.

**HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

001Games.com uses your personal information to:

Ask you to participate in surveys;

Offer you product upgrades, content, services and games;

Auto-update downloaded products; and Provide you with news, updates, targeted advertising, promotions, and special offers.

**WHAT NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**

We collect non-personal information that does not permit direct association with any specific individual. We may collect, use, transfer, and disclose non-personal information for any purpose. The following are examples of non-personal information that we collect:

Information about your computer, hardware, software, platform, mobile device, Internet Protocol (IP) address;

Language preference;

Anonymous information regarding customer activities on our websites, which is aggregated and considered non-personal information for purposes of this Privacy Policy.

**HOW DO WE USE YOUR NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

Improve our websites by providing content recommendations, language and location customization, targeted advertising and/or personalized help and instructions;

Determine if you meet the minimum system requirements to use our products, and provide information concerning compatibility and interoperability;

Better understand how our products are used.

**THIRD PARTY ADVERTISING**

We allow third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our websites or interact with our products or services. These companies use non-personal information about your visits in order to provide advertisements of interest to you.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g. click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information.

**USE OF COOKIES**

We use cookies, web beacons, pixel tags, and similar technologies to provide you with a tailored experience.

**CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

We frequently revise this Privacy Policy to keep it up to date with 001Games.com web pages.
